shoperskart.com 2015-10-12

# Shoperskart.com | Online Shopping India | Buy Mobiles, Cameras, Electronics, Accessories, Lifestyle Products ,online Shopping for Branded Shoes, Clothing & Accessories in India | Shoperskart.com

## Privacy Policy and Disclaimer

Protecting your privacy is very important to us. We have accordingly developed this Privacy Policy to protect your personal information and keep it confidential. We Endeavour to comply with laws of other countries but cannot and do not warrant that we do. We do everything we reasonably can to protect your rights of privacy on systems and the Website controlled by us, but we are not liable for any unauthorized or unlawful disclosures of your personal and confidential information made by third parties who are not subject to our control, for example advertisers and websites that have links to our Website. You should take note that the information and privacy practices of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide hyperlinks, may be different from ours. Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.

Information which you provide when you register for a Service, which may include some or all of the following: - Information about your personal identity such as gender, marital status, age, preferences, likes and dislikes etc.; - Your financial information such as your banking details and any information relating to your income and lifestyle levels; and - Your contact details such as your physical addresses, postal addresses, telephone and fax numbers and the like. - In the case of Facebook aligned services (if so opted by you), publicly available information of your friends, their likes and dislikes, Your account history with us including (without limitation) all billing information and communications, payment history etc. We maintain this in encrypted form on secure servers. Information about your navigation using our Services, for example the URLs of websites, which you visit and from which you request downloads. Information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, date and time of requestContent, information about your correspondents, and the destination/origin of communications between you and any other person using our Services, which include email communications, blog, chat room and discussion board communications, instant message communications, experts forum communications, faxmail communications, membership of mailing lists etc. Your usernames, passwords, email addresses and other security-related information used by you in relation to our Services. Data either created by you or by a third party and which you wish to store on our servers such as image files, documents etc.

We only collect your Personal Information to conduct our business and to enable us to deliver and improve our Services. We do not for any reason whatsoever sell your Personal Information to any third party or otherwise trade on it. We will only disclose your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy

## Anti-Spam Policy

Shoperskart has a no tolerance spam policy. Shoperskart customer support actively monitors large import lists and emails going to a large number of subscribers. Any customer found to be using Shoperskart for spam will be immediately cut-off from use of the product. If you know of or suspect any violators, please notify us immediately at abuse@sparrowsolution.com. Every email contains a mandatory unsubscribe link - those individuals who try to remove this link will be warned that they are doing so. If the link is removed or de-activated in any way, Shoperskart will terminate the customer's account. 

### What is Spam?

Spam is unsolicited email also known as UCE (Unsolicited Commercial Email). By sending email to only to those who have requested to receive it, you are following accepted permission-based email guidelines. 

### What constitutes a Preexisting business relationship?

The recipient of your email has made a purchase, requested information, responded to a questionnaire or a survey, or had offline contact with you. 

### What constitutes consent?

The recipient of your email has been clearly and fully notified of the collection and use of his email address and has consented prior to such collection and use. This is often called informed consent. 

### Isn't there a law against sending Spam?

The federal anti-spam law went into effect on January 1st, 2004 and preempts all state laws. While this new law will not stop spam, it does make most spam illegal and ultimately less attractive to spammers. The law is specific about requirements to send commercial email and empowers the federal government to enforce the law. The penalties can include a fine and/or imprisonment for up to 5 years. 

###  How Shoperskart protects you from sending spam

Shoperskart is a permission-based email-marketing tool that follows the strictest permission-based philosophies:  
**Communication** \- Your Shoperskart registration page already states why you are collecting the site visitor's email address, how you plan to use their address, and that you are following the embedded privacy policy. Additionally, by accepting our license agreement you have agreed to use only permission-based lists and never to sell or rent your lists.   
**Verification** \- Shoperskart automatically sends all of your new subscribers an email confirming their interest in receiving emails from you. Additionally, if your subscriber changes his or her interests or unsubscribes, Shoperskart automatically sends an email confirmation.   
**Unsubscribe** \- Every email generated from Shoperskart contains an unsubscribe link which allows your subscribers to opt-out of future email campaigns and automatically updates your subscriber lists to avoid the chance of sending unwanted emails to visitors who have unsubscribed.   
**Identification** \- Your email header information is correct because it is pre-set for you by Shoperskart. Your email campaign's "From" address is verified and already accurately identifies you as the sender.   
**Contact Information** \- all of your emails are pre-filled with your contact information including your physical address. 

### How to protect yourself from Spam: Take the Spam Test

Are you importing a purchased list of ANY kind? Are you sending to non-specific addresses such as: sales@domain.com, business@domain.com, webmaster@domain.com, info@domain.com, or other general addresses. Are you sending to distribution lists or mailing lists which send indirectly to a variety of email addresses? Are you mailing to anyone who has not explicitly agreed to join your mailing list? Have you falsified your originating address or transmission path information? Have you used a third party email address or domain name without their permission? Does your email's subject line contain false or misleading information? Does your email fail to provide a working link to unsubscribe? Are you failing to process any unsubscribe requests that come to you via a reply to your email within 10 days of the request?
